Come on.
Where are you going?
To the North.
For what?
What can I do as a businessman?
To do business.
Cousin Lunar.
Where are you going?
Cut the crap.
I gave you chicken drumsticks for nothing.
The Imperial Family wants you to die.
It wasn't me.
I can't lose the Camp.
Neither can the Shen Family.
Hey.
What kind of person
your mother was?
I have no mother since I was young.
I have a family business since childhood.
and family business.
I dare not rest for a moment.
I have a mother.
but I don't.
She's more like a courtesan.
She never cares about my thoughts and feelings.
They only urge me to work hard
to think more about my family.
But I think
she loves me too.
When I was young,
she also sang a song to make me sleep.
She made my favorite lotus seed soup.
Lotus seed soup?
Is it good?
Cousin Lunar.
Cousin Lunar!
Shen Mingyue.
What's wrong, Young Master?
She’s gone.
Did you see her go out?
I fell asleep.
But I didn't hear anything.
It's normal
she doesn't trust me.
Your Highness.
Lan Yu, you...
It's nothing serious.
Your Highness.
The Huo family has been exiled.
This is the route map.
Looks like we're sending them to the North.
More or less.
Let Ao Jia match some good fighters.
It's not a big problem.
There's a wasteland here.
It won't hurt the innocent.
It's perfect for action.
Yes, I'll make arrangements.
I will come back eventually.
Hurry up.
Mother.
Let's go.
Sir, give us some water.
Give us some water.
Leave if there's no water.
Hurry up.
Your Highness.
What brings you here?
I don't want to see you die.
Get up.
Come with me.
Mother.
Your Highness.
Ji Hong Zhen!
Come out!
Mother, you are so naughty.
No wonder Father wants to take back the Camp.
This is useful.
You're a scoundrel. You can't use it as a bait. You're a scoundrel.
How dare you use the Huo family as bait?
It's because you love this Huo kid so much.
You can't even escape, but you still want to save him.
How can he take care of you
can serve you?
It's none of your business.
Your Majesty, stay.
Kill the rest.
Blue Feather.
Lan Yu.
Mother.
Come back to the palace with me.
You're so naughty.
Why did you take the Royal Seal?
Give it to me.
Your Highness.
Ten years ago,
you saved me from the dogs,
and brought me into the Camp,
Lan Yu believed
to die for you.
Your Highness.
Lan Yu.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
Forgive me, Your Majesty!
Shen Mingyue!
Zhao Jin.
I know I’m handsome and handsome,
but my cousin
wouldn't have
so blindly.
White hair is your real hair.
Let me see your black hair again.
I have to give two rewards to watch acrobatics.
My cousin is penniless now.
How are you going to reward me?
It was you
was you, right?
Cousin.
Why do you say that?
There's a butterfly birthmark
on your wrist.
It's not him.
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
He Lian Jin.
What are you afraid of?
So what?
Do you dare to admit it?
No.
She obviously doesn't trust me now.
If I told her that I was the one who had the spring breeze that night,
she would kill me immediately.
Settlement?
Change.
and a crouch.
You can
in sorcery.
You must not be Nobody.
Who are you?
What do you want to do?
What do you want me to do to you?
What do you dare to do?
I dare to do
to do.
All right.
I did it on purpose.
I saw you overused your magic
and your blood stopped.
I'll give you some internal force.
Otherwise,
you'll be blind.
Such a beautiful girl
It's a pity to be blind.
Do I have to be grateful to you?
Is this dagger from the Heavenly Camp?
I can't recover in a month
I can't recover in a month.
Are you still angry?
If you dare to offend me again,
I'll kill you.
I knew I shouldn't tell her.
Otherwise,
she will kill me.
Mr. Zhao's hair
is a disguise.
Mr. Zhao's identity is a mystery.
Now he wants to go to the North with us.
I'm afraid he's up to no good.
Worried about me?
Your safety is important.
The night before you were arrested,
I summoned you to the palace.
When did you leave the palace at night?
At midnight.
Where were you before leaving the palace?
In the study of Fengyi Palace.
Is there anyone with you?
No.
I was alone.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
That night,
someone
stole the ledger of the gold case.
I’m sure
that person is Zhao Jin.
But besides him,
another thief
broke into my palace.
Can I see your wrist?
Your Highness, please behave yourself.
Leave now.
Pull and pull.
Waiting for pursuers?